Guide to the Wilkins Media Company Records, 1967-1998 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Materials, 1984-1998, (3 Boxes)
  - Outdoor Network, USA. Superflex: A New Dimension in Creative Outdoor. VHS. TRT: 10:00. 1987 June. (Box 22)
  - Powervision. We've Got the Power. VHS. TRT: 3:00. 1998 Jan. 14. (Box 22)
  - Profile Systems. Problems... Solutions. VHS. TRT: 6:21. 1995. (Box 22)
  - Profile Systems. A Sign of the Future in Outdoor communications Solutions. VHS. TRT: 8:30. undated (Box 22)
  - R. C. Maxwell Company. A Visual History of the R. C. Maxwell Company. VHS. TRT: about 5:00. circa 1994. (Box 22)
  - Skyway Ads. VHS. TRT: about 2:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Streetblimps. The Traveling Billboard... An Advertising Medium Whose Time Has come. VHS. TRT: about 2:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau. TAB Perspectives video--7 interviews. VHS. TRT: about 2:00:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Traffic Audit Bureau. OVRS. VHS. TRT: 8:13. 1989 Sept. (Box 22)
  - Target Markets Concepts. VHS. TRT: about 2:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Technique Mirage. Demo reel--version III. VHS. TRT: about 5:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Telecom Research Inc. Umatic. TRT: 10:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Tri-State Systems. BD #956 Cordele MP 102.76; BD #104 Cordele MP 102.50. VHS. TRT: about 2:00:00. 1995 Dec. 7. (Box 22)
  - USA Today. Gannett Outdoor: The Effect. VHS. TRT: 16:32. 1986 Apr. 18. (Box 22)
  - USA Today. Gannett Outdoor: Larger Than Life. VHS. TRT: 14:45. 1986 Apr. 18. (Box 22)
  - USA Today. Signs of the Times. VHS. TRT: 14:55. 1986 Apr. 18. (Box 22)
  - USA Today. Gannett Outdoor: Masterwork. VHS. TRT: 20:00. 1986 Apr. 18. (Box 22)
  - USA Today. A Passion for Excellence. VHS. TRT: about 60:00. undated (Box 22)
  - U.S. Surfing Tour. Promo 98. VHS. TRT: about 1:00. circa 1998. (Box 22)
  - Van Wagner Communications. Times Square, USA. VHS. TRT: 20:00min. undated (Box 22)
  - WNEP-TV 16. Wheels America. VHS. TRT: 10:00. 1996 June. [2 copies] (Box 22)
  - Wilkins Outdoor Network. Building Brands Beautifully. VHS. TRT: 20:00. undated (Box 22)
  - Producer unknown. 21st Century Marketing Tech, Inc. Real-time Creative Testing. VHS. TRT: 30:00. 1998 (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. Be It Ever So Humble. VHS. TRT: 2:00:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. Eye on L.A. VHS. TRT: 30:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. The Greatest Show on Earth (Miss America). VHS. TRT: 20:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. Lintas President & Creative Director interviews; TAB Perspectives--7 interviews on outdoor. VHS. TRT: 2:00:00. 1989 Apr. (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. L. Weaver--Ga. Lottery Market Ride; Columbus, Albany, I-75, Macon, I-85. VHS. TRT: 2:00:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. PM Magazine Car Billboard/IMO. VHS. TRT: 2:00:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. Think Biggest. VHS. TRT: 2:00:00. undated (Box 23)
  - Producer unknown. Vehicle Art Robo v7. VHS. TRT: 10:00. undated (Box 23)
- Oversized Material, 1979-1993 and undated, (1 box)
  - Printed Material, 1979-1993 and undated (Oversize-box OV1)
    - Gannett Outdoor Network USA Guide to Out-of-Home, 1993 (Oversize-box OV1)
    - Kraft--picture of Freshness, 1979 (Oversize-box OV1)
    - The Unbreakables, undated (Oversize-box OV1)